<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HW4</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo2">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_information_book_app">The information book app</string>
    <string name="the_countries">The Countries</string>
    <string name="the_leaders">The Leaders</string>
    <string name="todo3">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo4">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_museums">The Museums</string>
    <string name="the_seven_wonders_of_the_world">The Seven Wonders of The World</string>
    <string name="uk">UK</string>
    <string name="france">France</string>
    <string name="italy">italy</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="italytest">ITALY</string>
    <string name="notjing">NOTJING</string>
    <string name="ukflag">TODO</string>
    <string name="capital_london_n">Capital : London\n</string>
    <string name="largest_city_london_n">Largest City : London\n</string>
    <string name="national_language_english_n">National Language : English\n</string>
    <string name="total_area_242_495_km_n">Total Area : 242,495 km²\n</string>
    <string name="currency_gbp_n">Currency : GBP\n</string>
    <string name="n_the_united_kingdom_of_great_britain_and_northern_ireland_commonly_known_as_the_united_kingdom_uk_or_britain_is_a_country_in_northwestern_europe_off_the_coast_of_the_continental_mainland_it_comprises_england_scotland_wales_and_northern_ireland_the_uk_includes_the_island_of_great_britain_the_north_eastern_part_of_the_island_of_ireland_and_most_of_the_smaller_islands_within_the_british_isles_covering_244_376_km_northern_ireland_shares_a_land_border_with_the_republic_of_ireland_otherwise_the_united_kingdom_is_surrounded_by_the_atlantic_ocean_the_north_sea_the_english_channel_the_celtic_sea_and_the_irish_sea">\n The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the coast of the continental mainland. It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. The UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles, covering 244,376 km². Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland; otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea, and the Irish Sea.</string>
    <string name="italyflag">TODO</string>
    <string name="capital_rome_n">Capital : Rome\n</string>
    <string name="largest_city_rome_n">Largest City : Rome\n</string>
    <string name="national_language_italian_n">National Language : Italian\n</string>
    <string name="total_area_301_340_km_n">Total Area : 301,340 km²\n</string>
    <string name="currency_euro_eur_n">Currency : Euro (EUR)\n</string>
    <string name="n_italy_a_officially_the_italian_republic_b_is_a_country_in_southern_and_western_europe_c_it_consists_of_a_peninsula_that_extends_into_the_mediterranean_sea_with_the_alps_on_its_northern_land_border_as_well_as_nearly_800_islands_notably_sicily_and_sardinia_italy_shares_land_borders_with_france_to_the_west_switzerland_and_austria_to_the_north_slovenia_to_the_east_and_the_two_enclaves_of_vatican_city_and_san_marino_it_is_the_tenth_largest_country_in_europe_by_area_covering_301_340_km2_116_350_sq_mi_and_the_third_most_populous_member_state_of_the_european_union_with_nearly_59_million_inhabitants_italy_s_capital_and_largest_city_is_rome_other_major_cities_include_milan_naples_turin_palermo_bologna_florence_genoa_and_venice_the_history_of_italy_goes_back_to_numerous_italic_peoples_notably_including_the_ancient_romans_who_conquered_the_mediterranean_world_during_the_roman_republic_and_ruled_it_for_centuries_during_the_roman_empire_with_the_spread_of_christianity_rome_became_the_seat_of_the_catholic_church_and_the_papacy_barbarian_invasions_and_other_factors_led_to_the_decline_and_fall_of_the_western_roman_empire_between_late_antiquity_and_the_early_middle_ages_by_the_11th_century_italian_city_states_and_maritime_republics_expanded_bringing_renewed_prosperity_through_commerce_and_laying_the_groundwork_for_modern_capitalism_the_italian_renaissance_flourished_during_the_15th_and_16th_centuries_and_spread_to_the_rest_of_europe_italian_explorers_discovered_new_routes_to_the_far_east_and_the_new_world_contributing_significantly_to_the_age_of_discovery_after_centuries_of_political_and_territorial_divisions_italy_was_almost_entirely_unified_in_1861_following_wars_of_independence_and_the_expedition_of_the_thousand_establishing_the_kingdom_of_italy_from_the_late_19th_to_the_early_20th_century_italy_rapidly_industrialised_mainly_in_the_north_and_acquired_a_colonial_empire_while_the_south_remained_largely_impoverished_fueling_a_large_immigrant_diaspora_to_the_americas_from_1915_to_1918_italy_took_part_in_world_war_i_with_the_entente_against_the_central_powers_in_1922_the_italian_fascist_dictatorship_was_established_during_world_war_ii_italy_was_first_part_of_the_axis_until_its_surrender_to_the_allied_powers_1940_1943_then_a_co_belligerent_of_the_allies_during_the_italian_resistance_and_the_liberation_of_italy_1943_1945_following_the_war_the_monarchy_was_replaced_by_a_republic_and_the_country_enjoyed_a_strong_recovery_a_developed_country_with_an_advanced_economy_italy_has_the_eighth_largest_nominal_gdp_in_the_world_the_second_largest_manufacturing_sector_in_europe_and_plays_a_significant_role_in_regional_and_to_a_lesser_extent_global_economic_military_cultural_and_political_affairs_italy_is_a_founding_and_leading_member_of_the_european_union_and_is_part_of_numerous_other_international_organizations_and_forums_as_a_cultural_superpower_italy_has_long_been_a_renowned_global_centre_of_art_music_literature_cuisine_fashion_science_and_technology_and_the_source_of_multiple_inventions_and_discoveries_it_has_the_highest_number_of_world_heritage_sites_60_and_is_the_fourth_most_visited_country_in_the_world">\n Italy,[a] officially the Italian Republic,[b] is a country in Southern and Western Europe.[c] It consists of a peninsula that extends into the Mediterranean Sea, with the Alps on its northern land border, as well as nearly 800 islands, notably Sicily and Sardinia. Italy shares land borders with France to the west; Switzerland and Austria to the north; Slovenia to the east; and the two enclaves of Vatican City and San Marino. It is the tenth-largest country in Europe by area, covering 301,340 km2 (116,350 sq mi), and the third-most populous member state of the European Union, with nearly 59 million inhabitants. Italy\'s capital and largest city is Rome; other major cities include Milan, Naples, Turin, Palermo, Bologna, Florence, Genoa, and Venice. The history of Italy goes back to numerous Italic peoples—notably including the ancient Romans, who conquered the Mediterranean world during the Roman Republic and ruled it for centuries during the Roman Empire. With the spread of Christianity, Rome became the seat of the Catholic Church and the Papacy. Barbarian invasions and other factors led to the decline and fall of the Western Roman Empire between late antiquity and the Early Middle Ages. By the 11th century, Italian city-states and maritime republics expanded, bringing renewed prosperity through commerce and laying the groundwork for modern capitalism. The Italian Renaissance flourished during the 15th and 16th centuries and spread to the rest of Europe. Italian explorers discovered new routes to the Far East and the New World, contributing significantly to the Age of Discovery. After centuries of political and territorial divisions, Italy was almost entirely unified in 1861, following wars of independence and the Expedition of the Thousand, establishing the Kingdom of Italy. From the late 19th to the early 20th century, Italy rapidly industrialised—mainly in the north—and acquired a colonial empire, while the south remained largely impoverished, fueling a large immigrant diaspora to the Americas. From 1915 to 1918, Italy took part in World War I with the Entente against the Central Powers. In 1922, the Italian fascist dictatorship was established. During World War II, Italy was first part of the Axis until its surrender to the Allied powers (1940–1943), then a co-belligerent of the Allies during the Italian resistance and the liberation of Italy (1943–1945). Following the war, the monarchy was replaced by a republic and the country enjoyed a strong recovery. A developed country with an advanced economy, Italy has the eighth-largest nominal GDP in the world, the second-largest manufacturing sector in Europe, and plays a significant role in regional and—to a lesser extent—global economic, military, cultural, and political affairs. Italy is a founding and leading member of the European Union, and is part of numerous other international organizations and forums. As a cultural superpower, Italy has long been a renowned global centre of art, music, literature, cuisine, fashion, science and technology, and the source of multiple inventions and discoveries. It has the highest number of World Heritage Sites (60) and is the fourth-most visited country in the world.</string>
    <string name="franceflag">TODO</string>
    <string name="capital_paris_n">Capital : Paris\n</string>
    <string name="largest_city_paris_n">Largest City : Paris\n</string>
    <string name="national_language_french_n">National Language : French\n</string>
    <string name="total_area_551_695_km_n">Total Area : 551,695 km²\n</string>
    <string name="currency_euro_eur_n_france">Currency : Euro (EUR)\n</string>
    <string name="n_france_i_officially_the_french_republic_j_is_a_country_located_primarily_in_western_europe_its_overseas_regions_and_territories_include_french_guiana_in_south_america_saint_pierre_and_miquelon_in_the_north_atlantic_the_french_west_indies_and_many_islands_in_oceania_and_the_indian_ocean_giving_it_one_of_the_largest_discontiguous_exclusive_economic_zones_in_the_world_metropolitan_france_shares_borders_with_belgium_and_luxembourg_to_the_north_germany_to_the_northeast_switzerland_to_the_east_italy_and_monaco_to_the_southeast_andorra_and_spain_to_the_south_and_a_maritime_border_with_the_united_kingdom_to_the_northwest_its_metropolitan_area_extends_from_the_rhine_to_the_atlantic_ocean_and_from_the_mediterranean_sea_to_the_english_channel_and_the_north_sea_its_eighteen_integral_regions_five_of_which_are_overseas_span_a_combined_area_of_632_702_km2_244_288_sq_mi_and_have_an_estimated_total_population_of_over_68_6_million_as_of_january_2025_france_is_a_semi_presidential_republic_and_its_capital_largest_city_and_main_cultural_and_economic_centre_is_paris_metropolitan_france_was_settled_during_the_iron_age_by_celtic_tribes_known_as_gauls_before_rome_annexed_the_area_in_51_bc_leading_to_a_distinct_gallo_roman_culture_in_the_early_middle_ages_the_franks_formed_the_kingdom_of_francia_which_became_the_heartland_of_the_carolingian_empire_the_treaty_of_verdun_of_843_partitioned_the_empire_with_west_francia_evolving_into_the_kingdom_of_france_in_the_high_middle_ages_france_was_a_powerful_but_decentralized_feudal_kingdom_but_from_the_mid_14th_to_the_mid_15th_centuries_france_was_plunged_into_a_dynastic_conflict_with_england_known_as_the_hundred_years_war_in_the_16th_century_french_culture_flourished_during_the_french_renaissance_and_a_french_colonial_empire_emerged_internally_france_was_dominated_by_the_conflict_with_the_house_of_habsburg_and_the_french_wars_of_religion_between_catholics_and_huguenots_france_was_successful_in_the_thirty_years_war_and_further_increased_its_influence_during_the_reign_of_louis_xiv_the_french_revolution_of_1789_overthrew_the_ancien_r_gime_and_produced_the_declaration_of_the_rights_of_man_which_expresses_the_nation_s_ideals_to_this_day_france_reached_its_political_and_military_zenith_in_the_early_19th_century_under_napoleon_bonaparte_subjugating_part_of_continental_europe_and_establishing_the_first_french_empire_the_collapse_of_the_empire_initiated_a_period_of_relative_decline_in_which_france_endured_the_bourbon_restoration_until_the_founding_of_the_french_second_republic_which_was_succeeded_by_the_second_french_empire_upon_napoleon_iii_s_takeover_his_empire_collapsed_during_the_franco_prussian_war_in_1870_this_led_to_the_establishment_of_the_third_french_republic_and_subsequent_decades_saw_a_period_of_economic_prosperity_and_cultural_and_scientific_flourishing_known_as_the_belle_poque_france_was_one_of_the_major_participants_of_world_war_i_from_which_it_emerged_victorious_at_great_human_and_economic_cost_it_was_among_the_allies_of_world_war_ii_but_it_surrendered_and_was_occupied_in_1940_following_its_liberation_in_1944_the_short_lived_fourth_republic_was_established_and_later_dissolved_in_the_course_of_the_defeat_in_the_algerian_war_the_current_fifth_republic_was_formed_in_1958_by_charles_de_gaulle_algeria_and_most_french_colonies_became_independent_in_the_1960s_with_the_majority_retaining_close_economic_and_military_ties_with_france_france_retains_its_centuries_long_status_as_a_global_centre_of_art_science_and_philosophy_it_hosts_the_fourth_largest_number_of_unesco_world_heritage_sites_and_is_the_world_s_leading_tourist_destination_having_received_100_million_foreign_visitors_in_2023_a_developed_country_france_has_a_high_nominal_per_capita_income_globally_and_its_advanced_economy_ranks_among_the_largest_in_the_world_by_both_nominal_gdp_and_ppp_adjusted_gdp_it_is_a_great_power_being_one_of_the_five_permanent_members_of_the_united_nations_security_council_and_an_official_nuclear_weapon_state_the_country_is_part_of_multiple_international_organizations_and_forums">\n France,[i] officially the French Republic,[j] is a country located primarily in Western Europe. Its overseas regions and territories include French Guiana in South America, Saint Pierre and Miquelon in the North Atlantic, the French West Indies, and many islands in Oceania and the Indian Ocean, giving it one of the largest discontiguous exclusive economic zones in the world. Metropolitan France shares borders with Belgium and Luxembourg to the north; Germany to the northeast; Switzerland to the east; Italy and Monaco to the southeast; Andorra and Spain to the south; and a maritime border with the United Kingdom to the northwest. Its metropolitan area extends from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean and from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea. Its eighteen integral regions—five of which are overseas—span a combined area of 632,702 km2 (244,288 sq mi) and have an estimated total population of over 68.6 million as of January 2025. France is a semi-presidential republic and its capital, largest city and main cultural and economic centre is Paris. Metropolitan France was settled during the Iron Age by Celtic tribes known as Gauls before Rome annexed the area in 51 BC, leading to a distinct Gallo-Roman culture. In the Early Middle Ages, the Franks formed the kingdom of Francia, which became the heartland of the Carolingian Empire. The Treaty of Verdun of 843 partitioned the empire, with West Francia evolving into the Kingdom of France. In the High Middle Ages, France was a powerful but decentralized feudal kingdom, but from the mid-14th to the mid-15th centuries, France was plunged into a dynastic conflict with England known as the Hundred Years\' War. In the 16th century, French culture flourished during the French Renaissance and a French colonial empire emerged. Internally, France was dominated by the conflict with the House of Habsburg and the French Wars of Religion between Catholics and Huguenots. France was successful in the Thirty Years\' War and further increased its influence during the reign of Louis XIV. The French Revolution of 1789 overthrew the Ancien Régime and produced the Declaration of the Rights of Man, which expresses the nation\'s ideals to this day. France reached its political and military zenith in the early 19th century under Napoleon Bonaparte, subjugating part of continental Europe and establishing the First French Empire. The collapse of the empire initiated a period of relative decline, in which France endured the Bourbon Restoration until the founding of the French Second Republic which was succeeded by the Second French Empire upon Napoleon III\'s takeover. His empire collapsed during the Franco-Prussian War in 1870. This led to the establishment of the Third French Republic, and subsequent decades saw a period of economic prosperity and cultural and scientific flourishing known as the Belle Époque. France was one of the major participants of World War I, from which it emerged victorious at great human and economic cost. It was among the Allies of World War II, but it surrendered and was occupied in 1940. Following its liberation in 1944, the short-lived Fourth Republic was established and later dissolved in the course of the defeat in the Algerian War. The current Fifth Republic was formed in 1958 by Charles de Gaulle. Algeria and most French colonies became independent in the 1960s, with the majority retaining close economic and military ties with France. France retains its centuries-long status as a global centre of art, science, and philosophy. It hosts the fourth-largest number of UNESCO World Heritage Sites and is the world\'s leading tourist destination, having received 100 million foreign visitors in 2023. A developed country, France has a high nominal per capita income globally, and its advanced economy ranks among the largest in the world by both nominal GDP and PPP-adjusted GDP. It is a great power, being one of the five permanent members of the United Nations Security Council and an official nuclear-weapon state. The country is part of multiple international organizations and forums.</string>
    <string name="donald_trump">Donald Trump</string>
    <string name="putin">Putin</string>
    <string name="xi_jinping">Xi Jinping</string>
    <string name="le1">TODO</string>
    <string name="donald_john_trump_is_an_american_politician_media_personality_and_businessman_who_is_the_47th_president_of_the_united_states_a_member_of_the_republican_party_he_served_as_the_45th_president_from_2017_to_2021">Donald John Trump is an American politician, media personality, and businessman who is the 47th president of the United States. A member of the Republican Party, he served as the 45th president from 2017 to 2021</string>
    <string name="le2">TODO</string>
    <string name="vladimir_vladimirovich_putin_is_a_russian_politician_and_former_intelligence_officer_who_has_served_as_president_of_russia_since_2012_having_previously_served_from_2000_to_2008_putin_also_served_as_prime_minister_of_russia_from_1999_to_2000_and_again_from_2008_to_2012_he_is_the_longest_serving_russian_president_since_the_independence_of_russia_from_the_soviet_union_putin_worked_as_a_kgb_foreign_intelligence_officer_for_16_years_rising_to_the_rank_of_lieutenant_colonel">Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin is a Russian politician and former intelligence officer who has served as President of Russia since 2012, having previously served from 2000 to 2008. Putin also served as Prime Minister of Russia from 1999 to 2000 and again from 2008 to 2012. He is the longest-serving Russian president since the independence of Russia from the Soviet Union. Putin worked as a KGB foreign intelligence officer for 16 years, rising to the rank of lieutenant colonel.</string>
    <string name="le3">TODO</string>
    <string name="xi_jinping_a_born_15_june_1953_is_a_chinese_politician_who_has_been_the_general_secretary_of_the_chinese_communist_party_ccp_and_chairman_of_the_central_military_commission_cmc_and_thus_the_paramount_leader_of_china_since_2012_since_2013_xi_has_also_served_as_the_seventh_president_of_china_as_a_member_of_the_fifth_generation_of_chinese_leadership_xi_is_the_first_ccp_general_secretary_born_after_the_establishment_of_the_people_s_republic_of_china_prc">Xi Jinping[a] (born 15 June 1953) is a Chinese politician who has been the general secretary of the Chinese Communist Party (CCP) and chairman of the Central Military Commission (CMC), and thus the paramount leader of China, since 2012. Since 2013, Xi has also served as the seventh president of China. As a member of the fifth generation of Chinese leadership, Xi is the first CCP general secretary born after the establishment of the People\'s Republic of China (PRC).</string>
    <string name="mu1">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_louvre_is_the_world_s_largest_art_museum_located_in_paris_france">The Louvre is the world\'s largest art museum located in Paris, France.</string>
    <string name="mu2">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_british_museum_in_london_is_dedicated_to_human_history_art_and_culture">The British Museum in London is dedicated to human history, art, and culture.</string>
    <string name="mu3">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_metropolitan_museum_of_art_or_the_met_is_located_in_new_york_city">The Metropolitan Museum of Art, or \'the Met\', is located in New York City.</string>
    <string name="mus">Mus</string>
    <string name="e">E</string>
    <string name="um">um</string>
    <string name="colosseum">Colosseum</string>
    <string name="temple">Temple</string>
    <string name="rio_s_statue">Rio\'s statue</string>
    <string name="the_first_wonder_is_very_beautiful">The first wonder is very beautiful</string>
    <string name="this_one_is_very_nice">This one is very nice</string>
    <string name="this_one_not_my_fav_but_still_nice">This one not my fav but still nice</string>
</resources>